

josh@designerdean.com 801-999-0307 9124 Daybreak Circle Sandy, UT 84093 www.designerdean.com twitter.com/designer dean codepen.io/designerdean dribbble.com/designerdean

Profile: Hardworking and highly organized User Experience Designer/Engineer with 7 years of experience. Currently in an agency setting at Saxton Horne Communications, directing the Digital Department.

EXPERIENCE

Saxton Horne Communications in Sandy, Utah from February 2012 to Present Digital Team Manager & User Experience Lead

- · Directing and managing members of Digital department including user experience designers and backend engineers
- Leading the creation of client websites through information architecture, wireframes, prototypes, design, and development

a la mode, inc. in Salt Lake City, Utah from September 2010 to February 2012 **Product Designer**

- Designed and developed HTML/CSS of FormMobi.com web application UI
- · Redefined and redesigned website products for real estate professionals

IBFX in Salt Lake City, Utah from November 2007 to September 2010 **Web Designer**

- Led redesign of domestic and international customer websites including information architecture, wireframes, prototypes, design mockups, and front-end development
- Designed and developed HTML/CSS of corporate website and blog
- Designed and developed HTML emails and landing pages

Eastland Properties, Inc. in Holladay, Utah from August 2004 to November 2007 **REALTOR® / Web Designer**

- Marketed properties for sale to potential buyers, established and met contract deadlines and obligations
- Designed and developed brokerage website focused on marketing to potential clients

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF DENVER

Master of Communication with a specialty in Public Relations and Marketing, To be awarded December 2014

UNIVERSITY OF UTAH

Bachelor of Arts in English, Awarded 2006

SKILLS & INTERESTS

HTML & CSS (I like using Sass)

Responsive web design

Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, etc.)